Subindex build by Linnet
http://linnet.126.com  http://blog.csdn.net/redbirdli
火鸟字幕合并器SubindexV0.5
Created time 11.02.23 09:09:15
总统先生?
Mr President?
我们需要医疗援助!救命!
We need medical assistance! Help!
三年后
以下事件发生于abc下午1点至2点之间
事件实时发生
主演；基佛.瑟德兰
伊莉莎.卡佛博特
卡洛斯.伯纳德
瑞珂.艾斯沃斯
詹姆斯.巴治.戴尔
丹尼斯.海斯伯特
我是警卫,大门处需要支援
This is security. l need help at the ramp.
确认,先生
Clear， sir.
确认
Clear.
请走过去那里,给他们证件
step over there， please.abcGive 'em lD.
好
There you go.
打开1号门
Open one.
你还好吧,杰克?
You OK， Jack?
只有等这个文件签了abc我才会觉得好些
l won't be OK until we get this thing signed.
我并不是指这个
That's not what l meant.
好,我们都到齐了
OK. We're all here.
-现在要讨论什么改变?abc-他们不是破坏协议
- What kind of changes are we talking about?abc- They're not deal breakers.
他仍要放弃那些恐怖组织
He's still gonna give up the terrorist cells.
我只要求进二级监狱.abc不是最高安全级别的
He just wants to go to a class 2 detention.abcNot maximum security.
-那你打算答应他?-是的
- You're giving him it?abc- Yeah.
若不把我的当事人关押abc在佛罗里达,他将很不高兴
My client's not happy thatabcyou won't hold him in Florida.
-他将到明尼苏达州abc-去佛罗里达州也没区别
- He's getting Minnesota.abc- Give him Florida. There's no difference.
我让你们完成工作,为何abc你们不让我完成工作呢?
l let you do yourjobs.abcWhy don't you let me do mine?
我们不希望在情况不明abc之下把他送去南方
We don't want this thingabcgoing south over some detail.
萨拉扎并不老实.无法预测abc他的动向,风险太大
salazar is unstable. We can't predict what'llabcpush his buttons. There's too much at stake.
你们去年花了一年才抓住abc萨拉扎,我对此深表敬意
l know you two spent the last yearabcgetting salazar and l respect that.
-但我必须遵守规定abc-路易斯,过来一下
- But there's a protocol that l have to follow...abc- Luis， come here for a second.
把他送到何处不重要abc若他不说话,什么也得不到
Putting him away is not the point. lf heabcdoesn't talk， we've accomplished nothing.
我不会浪费整整一年abc去捉一个毒贩子
l didn't lose a year of my lifeabcto arrest some drug dealer.
萨拉扎和世界恐怖组织abc有联系,要把他们一网打尽
salazar deals with terrorist cells around theabcworld. Bringing them down is our objective.
不过若你答应萨拉扎abc所有要求,他就会要求更多
l understand. But if you give salazarabceverything he asks for， he's gonna want more.
这就是协议,他将要接受
This is the deal. And he's going to take it.
这里
Here.
你最好别错
You better be right.
道格拉斯.你手里拿着的abc是否我未来的命运?
Douglas. ls that my lifeabcyou're holding in your hand?
已经准备好可以签字了
lt's ready to be signed.
杰克,你在吗?
Are you in there， Jack?
别想他了
(Douglas) Forget about Bauer.
我又怎能忘记把我abc送到这里来的人呢?
How can l forget aboutabcthe man who put me here?
他假装我的朋友
Pretended to be my friend.
杰克,我为你感到担心
l'm concerned about you， Jack.
你为了把我抓到这里所做的abc一切,没别人会做到
The things you did to get me here，abcl wouldn't wish on anyone.
面对现实吧abc你不会是以前的你
Let's face it， you'll never be the same.
我也一样
Hey. Neither will l.
我想我们是在同一条船上
so l guess we are in the same boat.
我要准备签名了,杰克.abc对我们来说是重要时刻
l'm about to name names， Jack.abcThis is a big moment for both of us.
这让我感到高兴
That makes me happy.
因为我们又联系到一起了
Because， you see， we are connected now.
我不知道,也许我们abc一直是这样的
l don't know. Maybe we always have been.
我把有改变的地方都做了标记
l marked the changes.
我没必要看那些abc我只需要一支钢笔
l don't need to see the changes.abcBut l do need the pen.
除非你要我用自己的血来签名
Unless you want meabcto sign it with my own blood.
真有意思,“我自己的血”
That's kind of funny - ''my own blood''.
在哪里签名,道格拉斯?
Where do l sign this， Douglas?
这里
Right here.
你做我的律师做得很好
You have done a good job as my counsel.
就如他们说的那样万事通abc但他们会打你主意
Been a go-to guy ， as they like to say hereabcin the states. But l think they're on to you.
而我觉得你不能保守秘密
And l don't think you haveabcwhat it takes to keep your mouth shut.
什么意思?
(Douglas) What do you mean?
混蛋
son of a bitch.
开门!
Open the door. Open the door!
快开门!
Do it now!
-快叫医生来!abc-这是你的错,杰克
- Get a medic in here. Now!abc- This is your fault， Jack.
-接着事情就会到你身上abc-那是威胁吗?
- And what happens next is on you， too.abc- What does that mean， huh? ls that a threat?
-蔡斯!-混蛋
- Chase!abc- son of a bitch.
-退后!-去散散步吧!
- Back off!abc- Take a walk!
你听到了吗?
Did you hear me?
接着发生的事情abc就会到你身上,杰克
What happens next is on you， Jack.
到你身上!
lt's on you!
-梅萨医生,尸体隔离了abc-尸体上有我名字?
- Dr Macer. We isolated the body.abc- You said my name was on it?
是的,在尸体的胸口
Yes. lt's on his chest.
做一个全面测试,我认为abc这个是III型肺部病毒
Run a full panel of tests to be sure， but l thinkabcwe're dealing with a pneumonic virus， type lll.
III型?那不就是你们abc组在做模拟实验的病毒?
Type lll? lsn't that the virus groupabcyour team's been doing simulations on?
我想这就是他们把尸体abc送到我这里的原因
l think that's why this was addressed to me.
-联系CTU了吗?-还没有abc我们一直在等你
- Has CTU been contacted yet?abc- No. We've been waiting for you.
开始肺部测试.abc我会联系CTU的艾梅达
Go ahead and start the pulmonary tests.abcl'll call Director Almeida.
总统到南加州了吗?
Hey. The President arrive at sC yet?
差不多了.我们正和特务abc机关的人进行交接
Just about. We're swapping our peopleabcnow secret service is in place.
他们正等待你对人手进行调配
They're waiting forabcyour resource assessment.
好,我会给他们打电话
All right， l'll call 'em.
-不是第一次了 -怎么了,亚
- l've had it， Tony ， l swear to God.abc- What's the problem， Adam?
别让克洛伊.奥布莱恩abc碰我的数据
Chloe O'Brian does not touch my data.
在外探员需要数据,会问abc杰克或你,然后你来告诉我
lf Field Ops wants something， she asks Jackabcor talks to you， then you tell me.
-她毁坏了什么东西吗?abc-这不是问题所在
- Did she damage anything?abc- That's not the point.
我的部门从没有过失误abc就是因为我所制订的规矩
My department has zero downtimeabcbecause of the procedures l put in place.
她毁坏了什么东西吗?abc那就算了吧
- Did she damage anything? Then let it go.abc- No...
我和杰克在不同部门abc但在同一屋檐下,明白吗?
Jack's got his department and l got mine. Butabcwe're all under the same roof， understood?
好,听好了.你正在给abc你自己和我们找麻烦
Good. Now， lighten up. You're gonnaabcdrive yourself and the rest of us crazy.
好的,稍等
All right. Hold on.
卫生部的桑妮.梅萨找你
sunny Macer from Health servicesabcis on the line.
-你是否听说过赫索格?abc-没有
- By the way ， have you heard from Hertzog?abc- No， not yet.
-你会得到那份工作的abc-没有我,你不会去兰利的
- Relax， Michelle， you're gonna get the job.abc- You're not going to Langley without me.
怎么了?
Hey. What's up?
-这事我说出来感到难过abc-你在说什么?
- This is one l'm sorry to be right about.abc- What are you talking about?
克迪拉病毒abc一种III型肺部病毒
Cordilla virus.abclt's a type lll pneumonic virus.
记得我提出过有一个abc菌株可能流落在外吗?
Remember l raised the possibilityabca strain could be out there?
-是的-就是这个
- Yeah.abc- lt is.
有人刚刚扔下了abc一具染上该病毒的尸体
someone just dropped off a dead bodyabcinfected with the virus.
那些人是认真的,炸掉abc大门吸引注意力,这是信息
These guys are serious. They blew up theabcdoor to get our attention. This is a message.
有人得到那种病毒abc并打算传播出去?
That somebody's got the virusabcand they're willing to release it?
正是如此
Yeah， exactly.
我们是否要提出隔离建议?
Do we need to issue a quarantine advisory?
不.一旦宿主死亡,病毒abc就没有了传染性
No. Once the host is dead it's not contagious.
致电周边城镇,看abc是否发现其他病例
Call the other county facilities，abcsee if there are any more cases.
-怎确认尸体身份?abc-把资料都送到这里处理
- What about the lD on the John Doe?abc- send everything over. We'll work it up.
-正在路上-好的,谢谢
- lt's on its way.abc- All right. Thanks， sunny.
怎么了?
What is it?
宣布进入一级戒备状态
lnitiate a level one setting protocol.
而我觉得你不能保守秘密
(Salazar) And l don't think you haveabcwhat it takes to keep your mouth shut.
什么意思?
(Douglas) What do you mean?
萨拉扎过去三个月里可abc杀掉道格拉斯,为何选今天?
salazar could have killed shaye any timeabcover the last three months. Why today?
-他想破坏协议-可能吧abc但我不这么认为
- He was cutting his deal.abc- Maybe， but l don't think so.
这是你的错,杰克,接着abc发生的事情就会到你身上
This is your fault, Jack.abcAnd what happens next is on you, too.
“接着发生的事情”
''What happens next.''
-CTU-我是鲍尔.abc帮我接通艾梅达
- CTU.abc- This is Bauer. Patch me through to Almeida.
稍等
Hold on.
-嗨-有什么事发生了吗?
- （Tony) Hey.abc- ls anything going on there?
刚收到重要警报.这城市abc有可能遭到生化袭击
We just had a major protocol come in.abcPossible biothreat to the city.
告诉我详情
Tell me about it.
一具感染了克迪拉病毒abc尸体被遗弃在卫生部门口
A dead body infected with the Cordilla virusabcwas left at Health services.
这是第一个案例.我们abc在等承认责任的人
We figure it's the first shoe dropping. We'reabcwaiting for somebody to take responsibility.
-杰克?-是的
- Jack?abc- Yeah.
你认为这事和萨拉扎有关吗?
You thinking this is connected to salazar?
我不知道,也许吧
l don't know. l don't know， maybe.
-我会给你回电的-好
- l'll get back to you.abc- All right.
我需要所有4张图片的拷贝
- l need copies of all four images.abc- Right away.
南加州大学
(cheering)
-总统先生-维恩.abc准备好竞选连任了吗?
- Mr President.abc- Wayne. Are we ready for the run-through?
差不多了,前面的舞会abc还没完,暂时不能进去
Almost. The advance team dropped a ballabcso we can't get in there for a few minutes.
-那好吧-不好,我解雇abc茱迪,因她工作失误
- That's fine.abc- No， it's not fine. l fired Judy. lt was her fault.
她一直表现很好的,不是吗?
she's done some good work for us，abchasn't she?
今晚的辩论非常重要.她应该abc考虑到任何细节,但她没有
Tonight's debate is critical. she should haveabchad every single base covered but she didn't.
总统先生.你对你和参议员abc基勒之间的辩论有何感受?
Mr President. How do you feel aboutabcthe debate with senator Keeler?
充满自信,有备而战
Confident. Ready to go.
这是你自从上次袭击事件abc以来第一次回到洛杉矶
sir， this is your first time back to LAabcsince the attempt on your life.
-您对归来是否感到担忧?abc-一点也没有
- Were you uneasy about coming back?abc- Not at all.
洛杉矶是伟大的,若条件允许abc我本应该更早回来
Los Angeles is a great city. Would've beenabcback here sooner if events had allowed it.
最重要的是,我们abc要在这里展望未来
What is important is that we're here now，abclooking to the future.
谢谢,下午举行正式新闻发布会abc你们将得到简报
Thank you. That's all for now. We'll have aabcformal Q&A this afternoon. You'll be briefed.
大卫,我们要谈谈审计局abc那些数字.基勒今晚一定会说到
David， we gotta talk about those GAOabcmembers. Keeler's gonna bring it up tonight...
大卫?大卫,你没事吧?
David? David， are you all right?
我很好
l'm fine.
-我叫常驻医生过来abc-没什么,我等安妮过来
- Let me call one of the resident doctors.abc- No， it's all right. l'll wait for Anne.
-你要去哪里,杰克?abc我们必须谈谈-现在不行
- Where you going， Jack? We have to talk.abc- Not now.
-那什么时候?abc-给我打电话,现在要回CTU
- Then when?abc- Call me. Right now we gotta get to CTU.
为何?
Why?
萨拉扎杀死律师定有因abc选今天作案,我们要找到原因
salazar killed shaye for a reason. He pickedabctoday to do it. We gotta find out why.
好,我们回去把萨拉扎的嘴撬开
Fine. Let's go back in thereabcand put the screws on salazar.
你认为在看过他的表演后abc他还会说话吗?不可能
You think he's gonna talk to us afterabcwhat we just watched him do? Not a chance.
我们走吧
Come on. Let's go.
杰克
Jack.
给我打电话好了
Just call me.
关于那尸体艾梅达还说了什么?
All right， so what else did Almeida sayabcabout this dead body?
-杰克-怎么了?
- Jack.abc- What?
我在问你托尼的事情.abc他还说了什么?
l asked you about Tony.abcWhat else did he say?
他说尸体被扔在卫生部门口abc他们正在查明尸体身份
He said the body was dumpedabcat Health services. They're trying to lD it.
你之前从不回答我的问题.abc关于你的情况
You know， you never answered me before.abcAbout how you're doing.
-你在说什么?-你知道的
- What are you talking about?abc- You know what.
(phone rings)
-我是鲍尔-杰克,我是克洛伊
- This is Bauer.abc- Jack, it's Chloe.
凯特.华纳找你,要我接给你吗?
l have Kate Warner for you.abcShould l put her through?
Uh...
好的
Yeah. Put her through.
-杰克?-你好,凯特
- Jack?abc- Hi， Kate.
我刚找到你那件皮夹克abc你一直以为丢了
l just wanted to let you know l foundabcthat leatherjacket you thought you'd lost.
-太好了 -你想怎么办?
Oh. Uh...
- OK. Great.abc- So, uh, what do you want to do?
我可以带给你,或者寄给你
l could bring it over. Or send it.
不必那样.我派人到你那里拿
You don't have to do that.abcl'll just send someone over to pick it up.
-真的吗?-是的
- You sure?abc- Yeah.
-那好吧-凯特,你还好吗?
- OK， then.abc- Kate. How are you?
我知道这很不容易
You know， it's hard.
我想你
l miss you.
我真的很抱歉
l'm really ， really sorry.
别这样
Don't be.
-保重,凯特-再见
- Take care of yourself， Kate.abc- Bye.
-凯特怎样了?-她很好
- How's Kate?abc- she's all right.
-你俩还经常聊天?abc-其实并不是这样
- so you guys are still talking?abc- No， not really.
好了,与我无关的,不好意思
All right. None of my business. sorry.
我不是这个意思.abc她只是想还一些东西给我
l didn't mean it like that. she's just tryingabcto return a couple of things of mine， that's all.
有水吗?
Got any water?
我跟桑妮谈过,她正和其他机构abc联系看是否还有更多病例
Talk to sunny. she was checking withabcthe other facilities for any more cases.
若有的话,找到具体位置
lf there are， find out where.
找到所有地区具有的abc生化恐怖袭击的组织
Take all the regional cellsabcthat have bioterrorist capabilities
并把它们放到高速缓冲区里
and put 'em in a high-speed cache.
好
- OK.abc- (phone rings)
托尼,兰利的拉里.赫索格,在2线
Tony, it's Larry Hertzog from Langleyabcon line two.
你好,拉里
Hey ， Larry.
是的
Yeah， we are.
Uh-huh.
我会的,谢谢
Yeah， l will. Thanks.
-与我有关吗?-是的
- Was that about me?abc- Yeah.
他现在没有适合你的工作abc竞选后才会有新投资
He doesn't have ajob for you right now.abcThere's no new funding till after the election.
我明白
l see.
而且拉里还要求我abc今晚之前给他答复
Also， Larry told me that he needsabcan answer from me by the end of the day.
他们很迫切要填补这个职位
They're in a hurry to fill the post.
我们都知道你无法拒绝.abc这是一个重要的职位调动
We both know you can't pass this up.abclt's a major career move.
打电话给他说答应了
Call him and tell him it's yes.
而你会以妻子的身份跟我abc一起去?即使没有工作?
And you'll come along as the wife?abcWithout ajob?
你去哪里我都会跟着你
l'll go anywhere with you.
只要你不要求我做饭
As long as l don't have to cook.
宝贝,若你保证不做饭abc我到哪里都会带着你
sweetheart， if you promise not to cook，abcl will take you with me anywhere.
但若他们没工作给你abc我也不会感兴趣
But if they don't have ajob for you，abcl'm not interested.
托尼,国土安全部的人abc在1线
(phone rings)
Tony. Homeland Security on line one.
我们一会再谈吧
We'll talk about it later.
我是艾梅达
Almeida.
差不多了.只要刷新abc一下数据.谢谢
Pretty much. Just have to refreshabcthe data on my panel. Thanks.
-金姆-是的,米歇尔
- Hey ， Kim.abc- Yes， Michelle?
-完成可能性搜索了吗?abc-几周前我帮托尼做了一次
- You ever done a capability search?abc- Couple of weeks ago， for Tony.
-东欧组织那次?-是的
- The East European cells?abc- Yes.
好.这次有些难度.abc将是全球性的搜索
Good. This one's different.abclt's gonna be global.
-这是我的登陆密码abc-我马上去做
- Here's my access code.abc- l'll get right on it.
谢谢
Thanks.
亚当,链接文件是否使用DES加
Hey ， Adam.abcDoes the link file have DEs encryptions?
不,使用双密钥
No， it's two key.
-过滤程序在哪里?-E7
- What volume is the filter on?abc- Etude seven.
-谢谢-不客气
- Thank you.abc- You're welcome.
北墨西哥,拉斯尼耶维斯
-它的脾气很坏abc-也许它还没准备好
它准备好了.我从它眼里看出来
它让我想起你
你是说你要驯服我吗?
Are you saying you had to break me?
不,我的天使
No， mi angel.
是你驯服了我
lt was you who break me.
(phone rings)
怎样了?
, Que mas?
-他们得到那尸体abc-他们知道要应付何事?
我肯定他们知道了
搞定了吗?
, Seguro?
再给10分钟潜入系统
然后你再打电话
是的,先生
Si, senor.
好,结果出来了
OK， it's coming up now.
谢谢,克里斯
Thanks， Chris.
-亚当,我正把数据传到abc你的系统-什么数据?
- Adam， l'm piping this over to your system.abc- What is it?
卫生部门口尸体上的碎片.abc我们正在进行身份辨认
Frags on the body that was dropped off atabcHealth services. We're doing an lD analysis.
-你的可能性搜索呢?abc-正在运行,大概还要15分钟
- Where are you in the capability search?abc- lt's gonna be another 15 minutes.
-那你现在有空了?abc-你需要帮忙吗?
- so you're open?abc- What do you need?
亚当在分析DNA,我们需要abc这人的名字,把DNA文件给她
Adam'll break off part of an lD.abcWe need a name. Give her the file.
-我不需要她的帮助abc-你需要的
- l don't need her help.abc- Yes， you do.
这很紧急
This is urgent.
我准备好了,亚当.abc把文件发给我
l'm ready ， Adam. send the file.
-我打开了,亚当.abc把文件发给我-不
- l'm open， Adam. send me the file.abc- No.
-米歇尔刚告诉你了abc-我不需要任何人帮我
- Michelle told you...abc- l don't need anyone doing my work for me.
-你怎么了?-这里每人abc都凭本事得到工作
- What is your problem?abc- Everyone in this place earned theirjob.
而你是凭借你爸爸
You got it cos of your dad.
怎么回事?
What the hell is this?
(dials phone)
特蕾西,你的系统abc被锁住了吗?
- Tracy ， is your system locked?abc- No.
好,谢谢
OK， thanks.
你可能忘记设置小组许可了
lt could be you forgotabcto set the group permission.
某个了解树型结构的人abc把控制权改变了
someone who knowsabcthe tree structure changed the ownership.
但这不可能是我这无能的abc靠老爸才得到这工作的人
That wouldn't be me because l'm incompetentabcand only got this job because of my dad.
-金姆,把控制权改回去abc-把数据给我
- Change the ownership back， Kim.abc- send the data fork.
这是你的麻烦.米歇尔正等着
lt's your ass. Michelle's waiting.
好,我把数据给你.abc你给我的系统解锁
Fine. l'll send it. Just unlock my system.
没问题
No problem.
-杰克,我等会上去找你-好
- Hey ， Jack， l'll be up in a minute.abc- OK.
克洛伊,把资料给我
Chloe. Give me what you got.
我们和楼下的系统同步了吗?
Are we in sync with the systems?
卫生部送过来的资料abc都在第一卷
Everything Health services sentabcis in volume one.
-我已整理了萨拉扎的资料abc-数据库钥匙在哪里?
- l've reprised all the salazar information.abc- Where are the date keys?
-我不能给你-为何?
- l couldn't get those for you.abc- Why not?
你须请示托尼,他告诉亚当abc亚当才会把钥匙给我
You'll have to talk to Tony ， so he can tellabcAdam and Adam can give them to me.
-你在开玩笑吧abc-亚当讨厌女人
- You're kidding me， right?abc- No. Adam's anal and he hates women.
克洛伊
Chloe.
就去给我拿来,好吗?
Just get it for me， OK， please?
关门
Close my door.
(grunts)
(phone rings)
-喂?-我是米歇尔
- Yeah?abc- lt's Michelle.
与卫生部的电话abc会议马上开始了,你下来吧
The teleconference with Health Servicesabcis about to starty. Come down.
不,我就在这里.abc把他们接上来
No， l'm gonna stay up here.abcPatch them through.
-好-谢谢
- OK.abc- Thanks.
你吓到我了
You scared me.
-你来这里干什么?abc-我在刷新驱动器
- What are you doing in here?abc- l am refreshing a drive.
萨拉扎的事怎样了?abc你当时在场吗?
What's going on with salazar?abcWere you there when it happened?
是的
Yeah.
他真疯狂
Yeah， it was pretty crazy.
我爸爸怎样了?
How's my dad taking it?
-他很好-这就好
- He's OK.abc- Good.
我本想今天和他谈一谈
l was thinking about talking to him today.
-今天可不是最好时机abc-没有哪一天是最好的
Uh-huh.
- Today might not be the best day.abc- Chase， no day is a good day.
说好了,两个月后还在一起abc就要告诉他,都快3个月了
We said that we would tell him if we were stillabctogether after two months. lt's almost three.
为何不告诉他呢?
Why don't we just tell himabcand get it over with?
好吧
All right.
我会跟他说的
But l'll do it. OK?
-真的吗?-当然了
- Are you sure?abc- Yes， l'm sure.
-真的?-真的
- Really?abc- Really.
你不该把磁盘留在这里abc你应该看看.
You can't put the drives there.abcWhat l need you to do is look under...
-F6区,对吗?-对,谢谢
- F6， right?abc- Yeah. OK， thanks.
我们刚得到更多的化验结果
We received results of more tests.
但不是个好消息,这是abc一种生化武器类型的菌株
The news isn't good.abcThis is a weaponised strain.
病毒被改造,可以更迅速地致命
lt has been engineered to kill more rapidly.
有多迅速?
How rapidly?
基于验尸报告估计,若在零点感
lt's a bit of a guess but, based on the autopsy,abcif infection startys at Tequals zero hours,
前14小时是没有传染性的阶段
there's a noncontagious latency periodabcof 14 hours.
14小时后,症状出现,20小时后abc宿主丧失活动能力abc第24小时,宿主死亡
After 14 it presents. After 20 the hostabcis incapacitated. By 24 the host is dead.
若病毒蔓延会有什么后果?
What are the epidemiological consequences?
若病毒在某个地点开始爆发
If the virus initiates at a single location,
一天内将感染大约两百人
there will be a couple hundred casesabcby the end of day one.
两天内就会数以千计
By the end of day twoabcit could be in the thousands,
但那时还不必用人口的abc百分比来形容
but from there it's easier to talk aboutabcin percentage of population.
第一周过后,洛杉矶abc百分之九的居民将被感染
By the end of the fiirst week, nine per centabcof Los Angeles county will be infected.
百分之九?那就是超过一百万
Nine per cent?abcThat's over a million people.
并且这些人将在24小时内死亡
And those people will dieabcwithin 24 hours of infection.
若有人打算向公众散播这种病
so tell me， if someone were gonna try toabcrelease this virus into the general population，
他们要怎样做?
how would they do it?
很难知道,在任何地方abc都可以散播
That's the million-dollar question.abclt could come from anywhere.
我们不知道谁掌握着病毒abc也不知道将在哪里散播
We don't know who has it.abcWe don't know where they plan to release it.
甚至连病毒的存放形式abc也不知道
We don't even know what form it's in.
(~ ''Horse Drawn'' by Memory Bank)
凯尔?
- (knock at door)abc- (woman) Kyle?
怎么了,妈妈?
What， Ma?
-提姆在游泳池那里等你abc-谢谢,妈妈
- Tim wants you to know he's at the pool.abc- Thanks， Ma.
下午你能陪我去医院吗?
Can you take me to the doctorabclater on this afternoon?
-爸爸在干什么?abc-在准备工作面试.祝他好运
- What's Dad doing?abc- On ajob interview. Fingers crossed.
祝他好运
Fingers crossed.
诺玛阿姨可以陪你吗?
Can Aunt Norma take you?
为何?你有什么要事做abc而不能陪我去?
Why? What's so importantabcthat you can't take me?
我是说.
l mean...
我今天确实很忙,对不起,妈妈
lt's just l got a bunch of stuffabcto do today ， Ma. l'm sorry.
-那好,我打电话给诺玛abc-谢谢
- Fine. l'll call Norma.abc- Thanks.
我爱你,妈妈
Love you， Ma.
总统先生.在你遇刺后abc整个国家都震惊了
Mr President. The country was in shockabcafter the attempt on your life.
您幸免于难,人民都非常高兴
But its prayers were answeredabcwhen you survived.
很多人都担心您是否完全康复
That said， many Americans have expressedabcconcern that you are not fully recovered，
是否能在未来4年内继续工作
and are not strong enoughabcto serve for four more years.
您将如何回答?
How would you respondabcto those who make such claims?
每天早上5点我就起床
l wake up every morning at 5am.
在健身室里度过第一个小时
l spend the first hour in the weight room.
当我锻炼身体的时候,我也abc在为早晨的例会做准备
While l'm exercising，abcl'm prepping for my meetings.
-之后就是连续工作16小时abc-暂停!
- And then l put in a 16-hour day...abc- Hold on!
暂停录像好吗?倒回去
Could we pause the video， please?abcGet ready to play it back.
抱歉,查克.不要用防卫性的abc回答来解释这个问题
sorry ， Chuck. Hold on. Don't dignifyabcthat question with a defensive response.
我并不认为描述事abc实属于防卫性回答
l didn't realise that statingabcthe facts was being defensive.
他们以暗杀事件为话题abc这没问题.但你是命令其他人
They bring up the assassination attempt， fine.abcYou remind them it was your administration
抓捕暗杀事件幕后首脑的人
that arrested the manabcbehind the attempt on your life
并将其他组织分子一网打尽
and exposed his organisationabcand put his top-tier people away.
而这些事情都是你在abc“虚弱状态”下执行的
All this while you were inabcthis so-called ''weakened state''.
基勒若有你一半精力就很幸运abc这就是你要告诉他们的
Keeler would be lucky to have a fractionabcof your energy. That's what you tell 'em.
总统先生.继续吧,查克
Mr President. Go ahead， Chuck.
妈妈说我弟弟非常胆小呢
And Mom called him the timid brother.
我的医生来了.你好吗?
Ah， there's my doctor. How are you?
-总统先生-好,大家休息一下
- Mr President.abc- (Wayne) All right. Let's break for a minute.
我很好.总统怎样了?
l'm fine. How's he been?
-看起来有些疲倦abc-不累,只是有点不适应时差
- seems a little tired.abc- l am not tired. l'm just a little jet-lagged.
进展如何?
How's this going?
我一定可以赢得abc这次竞选连任
l'm definitely winning the run-through.
(phone rings)
-血压130/80-好.abc我是维恩.帕尔默
- 130 over 80.abc- Good. This is Wayne Palmer.
-你有多累?-我很好
- How tired?abc- l'm fine.
-我们来做一个快速检查abc-不要检查
- We haven't done a workup in a while...abc- No. No， no， no. No tests.
若开始寻找一样东西abc在没找到之前就不该停止
You start looking for somethingabcand you don't stop until you find it.
我很好,安妮
l'm fine， Anne.
好吧
OK.
在你回华盛顿后,要给你做abc彻底检查,这是医生命令
But when you get back to DC， l want you toabchave a complete physical. Doctor's orders.
遵命
Yes， ma'am.
安妮.我需要跟总统谈一下
Anne. l need him alone for a minute.
-他交给你了 -什么事情?
- He's all yours.abc- What is it?
我刚收到了卫生部打来的abc紧急电话
l just received a disturbing callabcfrom Health services.
在洛杉矶有人感染了一种abc非常危险而且致命的病毒
They found a body in Los Angeles that's beenabcinfected with a contagious and deadly virus.
他们认为这不是偶然事件
There's concernsabcit's notjust a random occurrence.
-意思是?-CTU正在调查.
- Meaning what?abc- CTU is looking to the possibility
这是否一次犯罪活动
that this could be a criminal action.
犯罪活动?就基于这一个死者?
Criminal action? Based on this one death?
细节我还不清楚
l don't know the details，
这是从验尸报告分析得来的
but it has to do with the circumstancesabcunder which the body was found.
-继续关注这件事情-好
- Keep your eye on this one.abc- OK.
查克,继续第7个关于abc国土安全的问题好吗?
Chuck， can we go down to question seven，abcabout homeland security?
-克洛伊-是
- Chloe.abc- Yes?
-萨拉扎文档在哪?abc-已发到你系统里,在目录下
- Where are the transcripts of salazar?abc- l sent them to your system, in your directory.
该死的,我要把它跟萨拉扎的abc其他文件存放在一起
Dammit， l wanted it storedabcwith the rest of the files from salazar.
好,我马上去做
OK. l'll do it.
克洛伊,若这些你也做不好abc我就找其他会做的人来
Chloe， if you can't get things rightabcthe first time， l can get someone who can.
你应该事先告诉我
lf you wanted it with the other filesabcyou should have said so.
-那不是按一般程序做的abc从现在开始就这么做
- That isn't standard， so l wouldn't do it.abc- Do it that way from now on， OK?
我不会看穿别人的思想.abc你应该跟我说明,不然.
l can't read minds. You'll justabchave to spell it out for me， otherwise...
该死的,克洛伊!现在就去做!
Dammit， Chloe! Just do it now!
好吧
Fine.
杰克
Hey ， Jack.
怎么了?
What?
-怎么了?-我需要你abc接替克洛伊的工作
- What was that all about?abc- l need you to replace Chloe for me.
接替她?她可是我们最好的abc分析专家
Replace her? she's the best analyst we got.
-她并不是,她动作太慢了abc-她动作不慢
- she's not. she's slow.abc- she's not slow.
她性格可能有些古怪abc但她对工作非常熟悉
she may be a little weirdabcbut she knows her stuff.
你看起来很糟糕
You look like hell.
你刚才说我什么?
What did you just say to me?
我们正处理一大事件,知道吗?abc我必须知道你能否胜任
We're on an active protocol， OK?abcl need to know if you're up for it or not.
我喜欢和你一起工作,蔡斯.abc你是个好伙计
l like working with you， Chase.abcYou're a nice kid.
但你别再进来这里跟abc我那样说话,明白了吗?
But don't you ever come into my officeabcand talk to me like that again. Understand?
我只是说你站在失控的边缘
l'm just saying you're on edge. OK?
你刚才还要无故地炒掉克洛伊
l mean， come on， man，abcyou're about to fire Chloe for no reason.
-克洛伊-是
- Chloe.abc- Yes?
刚才的事很抱歉,我们早上abc遇到不好的事情,希望你明白
l'm sorry l took your head off.abcWe're just having a bad morning， OK?
-谢谢-好
- Thanks.abc- Yeah.
你满意了吗?
You're happy?
杰克,我还想和你说一件事情
Look， Jack. There's one more thingabcl gotta talk to you about.
(phone rings)
-我是鲍尔-刚得到abc萨拉扎的最新线索
- This is Bauer.abc- （Tony) We've got something new on Salazar.
好,我们马上下去
OK， we'll be right down.
有萨拉扎的最新线索
They got something on salazar.
你想跟我说什么?
What do you wanna tell me?
没什么紧要的,以后再说吧
Nothing. lt'll hold.
好
Good.
为了堵住所有可能的安全漏洞abc我们开始日期检查
ln order to plug any possible securityabcbreaches， we'll do date checks from now on.
每隔8小时记录一次日志
Break your logs into eight-hour intervals.
每个时间段设置不同密钥.abc一个被破解,不会影响到其他
Put different encryptions on each interval. lfabcone is breached， one won't bleed to the other.
-你告诉他了吗?-没有.abc现在太忙了,我会说的
- Did you tell him?abc- No. There's a lot going on. lt'll happen.
10分钟前给FBI接到一个abc匿名电话.现在传送过来
An anonymous call came in to the FBl tenabcminutes ago. They're gonna stream it to us.
-你听过了吗?-是的
- Did you hear it?abc- Yeah.
-准备好了 -放出来
- OK. lt's ready.abc- Bring it up.
你们已经收到了我们的包裹abc并知道我们掌握着病毒
(distortyed) You've received our packageabcand realised we're in possession of a type lll
III型肺部病毒
pulmonary immuno virus.
仔细听好以下指引
Listen very carefully to these instructions.
我们的要求很简单
Our demand is very simple.
在6小时内释放萨拉扎
We want the releaseabcof Ramon Salazar in the next six hours.
若你们拒绝,病毒abc将在公众之中散播
If you refuse to comply, the virusabcwill be unleashed to the general population.
就如你们的专家所说那样abc你们无法阻止病毒的蔓延
As your expertys will tell you,abcyou will not have time to stop its spread.
如何释放萨拉扎的细节随后再
Details of how Ramonabcis to be delivered will follow.
-就是这些-知道电话abc在哪里打来吗?
- That's it.abc- Do we know where the call originated?
来自一些扰频的卫星信号.abc我们正在缩小范围
lt came out of a scrambled satellite signal.abcWe're trying to narrow it down.
你更了解萨拉扎.你认为abc我们跟何人打交道?
You know salazar better than anybody elseabchere. Who are we dealing with?
肯定是他弟弟abc赫克托是二号人物
His brother. Hector was next in command.
雷蒙被监禁后他就消失了
He went undergroundabcwhen Ramon was taken into custody.
我知道萨拉扎在南美和abc墨西哥拥有多处物业
Look. l know that the salazars own multipleabcproperties in south America and Mexico，
用虚假公司注册的
registered under dummy corporations.
不幸的是,墨西哥政府abc声称无法找到这些物业
Unfortunately ， the Mexican governmentabcis saying they can't locate them.
要找到电话的来源,我们abc必须撒下一个很大的网
We're gonna have to throw out a pretty largeabcnet to trace the origin of that call.
-我们会努力找到的abc-尸体的身份确认没有?
- We'll work on it.abc- How are we doing with the lD on the body?
-米歇尔正在检查DNAabc-指纹和牙科记录呢?
- Michelle's running the DNA.abc- What about prints and dental?
-尸体没有牙齿,没有指尖abc-必须知道他的身份
- No teeth， no fingertips.abc- We need this lD. lt's the only hook we've got.
为何不审问萨拉扎?
What about questioning salazar?
浪费时间.他根本不怕这些
Complete waste of time.abcThis is a man without vulnerability.
他不害怕审问,也不在乎abc任何亲人,包括他的儿子
He doesn't respond to interrogation or careabcabout a living soul， including his children.
托尼!找到了尸体的身份
Tony! We've a match on John Doe.
-看看-名字是大卫.高斯
- show us what you got.abc- The dead body is a David Goss.
洛杉矶东部的一个街头毒贩子abc也是一个线人
He's a street dealer in East LA，abcalso an informant.
他经常摇摆不定,毒品稽查局abc一年前已经中止与他的合作
He flipped sides so many timesabcDEA stopped working with him.
-有他最后出现的地址吗?abc-正在查找
- Last known address?abc- We're working on it.
要知道谁传染高斯.做一个abc最近一周跟他接触过的人的名
We need to know who infected Goss. Work upabca list of people involved in his life this week.
-把所有资料都集中起来abc-黑道那边也要去查
- We'll pull together everything we can.abc- Work it from the other side too.
通过萨拉扎的网络,调查abc谁给高斯提供毒品
Go through salazar's network.abcFind the supplier who sold to Goss.
做得好.蔡斯,跟我来.看看能否abc找到有关赫克托任何消息
Good work. Chase， come with me.abcLet's see if anything's come in on Hector.
-这是什么?-没用的东西
-这些不会影响我的土地吗?abc-不会的
小心一点
Entonces, asegurate. Que no se note nada.
是,先生
Si, senor.
浇上汽油
Ponle el petrol. Ponle fuego.
Sigue, ponle el petrol.
为何让我父亲为你干这种活?
Why do you have my fatherabcdoing this kind of work for you?
这并不是他的工作
lt's not his job.
今天而已
lt is today.
你为何要杀死你的律师?
Why did you kill shaye?
看看周围吧.你还在美国监狱abc你将在这里等死
Take a look around. You're in a Us prisonabcwhere your ass will rot until you're executed.
你想改善这里的生活条件abc那就最好跟我说话
You want to improve your conditions here，abcyou better start talking to me.
-你想说些什么?abc-为何要杀死你律师?
- What do you want to talk about?abc- Why did you kill your attorney?
-我不想让他和你说话abc-关于什么?
- l didn't want him talking to you.abc- About what?
关于一切
About anything.
这让你很难受,是吧?
lt's eating at you， isn't it?
你要拿我怎么办?路易斯
What am l up to? Come on， Luis.
把我锁在铁牢里abc叫两个大汉将我打扁
You have me in chains. Two tough guysabcwaiting for a chance to beat me to a pulp.
来吧,路易斯!
Do it， Luis!
看你能把我怎么办
see if you can beat it out of me.
你真没趣
You are no fun.
你要去哪?
Where are you going?
克劳迪亚
Claudia.
克劳迪亚!
Claudia!
怎么了?
What's wrong?
我父亲是个农场工头
My father is the ranch foreman.
你答应我不会把他拉下水的
You promised he wouldn't be involvedabcin your other activities.
我给你父亲3倍的价格.abc他可以多做一两个任务
l pay him three times over.abcHe can perform an extra task or two.
不,我们来这里居住的时候abc我就说了
No， no， no. No.abcl told you when we came to live here
我不要让他和我弟弟参abc与你那些非法活动
that l didn't want him or my little brotherabcto be exposed to your illegal business.
你违背了诺言,赫克托
You broke your word， Hector.
这伤害了我
And that hurts me.
真的伤害了我
lt hurts.
对不起,克劳迪亚
l'm sorry ， Claudia.
-我会补偿的-如何补偿?
- Please， l make it up to you.abc- How?
我给你父亲放假abc并多给他一个月工资
l give your father some time off.abcAn extra month's pay.
这就是你解决所abc有问题的方法,对吧?
That's your solutionabcto every problem， isn't it?
钱
Money.
克劳迪亚
Claudia.
克劳迪亚!
Claudia!
(phone rings)
-喂?-你给FBI打电话了吗?
- Yeah?abc- Have you made the call to the FBl?
打了
Yes， l did.
-那小子怎样了?abc-我正在监视他
- What about our boy?abc- l'm watching him now.
-要看好他-我会的
- Keep him close.abc- l will.
提华纳的小妞们好玩吧?
so what was it like to get knee-deepabcin some fine Tijuana dell?
-我没去找她们-什么?
Huh?
- l didn't do that.abc- What do you mean?
我不是去那里泡妞的
l mean l didn't go down there to get laid.
-但你说..abc-我知道我说了什么
- But you said...abc- No， l know. l know what l said.
我只是怕发生什么事情abc所以没说实话
l just didn't wanna tell youabcin case something happened.
那你的大秘密是什么?
so， what's the big secret?
记得高中时那个扎克.帕克吗?
Remember Zach Parker from high school?
当然.去年因为卖abc毒品被捉的那个
sure. Didn't he get busted last yearabcfor dealing coke?
是的
Yeah， yeah.
他把我推荐给这里的人
Whatever. He set me upabcwith this guy down there.
-推荐?你怎么认识他的?abc-我就认识他
- ''set you up''? How do you even know him?abc- l know him， OK?
你在搞什么?卖毒品?
What are you into here， man?abcAre you selling dope?
不是
No.
-我并不是卖什么..abc-那你到底在做什么?
- l'm not exactly selling anything...abc- Then exactly what are you doing?
那人给我5千块abc叫我带些可卡因过边境
This guy... he paid me five grandabcto bring some coke over the border.
我昨晚去了.今天再做abc一次,还能多拿5千
l did that last night.abcToday l drop it off， l get another five.
-你一定是疯了abc-就这一次而已
- You're outta your mind.abc- lt's just one time.
过境是最麻烦的.abc那已经搞定了
Getting over the border's the hard part.abcThat's already done.
你为何要这么做?
Why are you doing this?
我母亲正在做透析abc父亲失业了
Cos my mom's on dialysis.abcMy dad's out of ajob.
我们就要被人从那破公寓abc中赶出去.这够惨了吧?
We're about to get evicted from this crappyabcapartment. ls that good enough for you?
伙计,你真的疯了
Dude， you are seriously insane.
提姆
Look， Tim.
我打算今天晚些时候去交货.abc我想你可以跟我一起去
l'm about to make this drop later today.abcl was thinking， maybe we could go together.
-别想了!abc-你只需要在车上等着
- Forget it!abc- You just wait in the car.
我去交货,然后就走,就这么简单
l go in， l make the drop， l come back out.abcThat's it. There's no big deal.
我没兴趣
l'm not interested.
你再想想吧
Think about it.
(girl squeals)
总统先生
- Mr President， sir.abc- Mr President， sir.
各位继续
Carry on.
-FBI何时接到电话?abc-约20分钟前
- When did FBl get this call?abc- About 20 minutes ago.
-知道在跟谁打交道吗?abc那是通过公开线路打来的电话
- We don't know who we're dealing with?abc- lt was a scrambled voice on an open line.
他们要求释放萨拉扎abc不然就散播病毒
All we know is what he said. They wantabcsalazar or they're gonna release the virus.
你觉得怎样,维恩?abc要取消辩论会吗?
What's your take on this， Wayne?abcDo we cancel the debate?
目前为止,国防部,五角大楼abc以及CTU还没建议提升警戒等级
so far， DOD， the Pentagon and CTUabchaven't recommended raising the alert level，
不过他们正在讨论我们abc是否应该留在洛杉矶
but they are discussing whether or notabcwe should stay in Los Angeles.
-长官-亚伦
- sir.abc- Yes， Aaron?
派克医生来了.她想见你
Dr Packard's here. she's asked to see you.
-请告诉她我现在很忙abc-是,总统先生
- Tell her l'm busy ， please.abc- Yes， Mr President.
亚伦,等一等
Aaron， wait.
-告诉她,我会跟她谈谈abc-是,长官
- Tell her l'll speak with her.abc- Yes， sir.
你真的打算这样做吗?
You really wanna do that right now?
是的,维恩
Yes， Wayne， l do.
-安妮?-你要开始吃这些药
- Yes， Anne?abc- l want you to start taking these.
早上服一粒,晚上睡觉前abc再服一粒
One in the morning and one beforeabcyou go to bed. lt'll help your energy.
-我告诉过你我没事abc-我知道你说过
- l told you l was fine.abc- l know what you told me.
你相信你的医生吗?
Are you gonna trust your doctor or not?
我当然相信
Course l am.
发生什么事了?你看起来很焦虑
so， what's going on? You seem upset.
没什么
Nothing.
这只是像过去那些繁忙的abc日子中的一天
lt's just gonna be another one of those days.
什么意思?
What does that mean?
我得回去了
l've got to get back.
好
OK.
我们稍后再谈
We'll talk later.
-系统到底怎么了?-怎么了?
- What is wrong with this system?abc- What?
网格显示不出来
The grid won't come up.
你得按Ctl+S
That's because you needabcto ''control s'' out of it.
现在还是浏览模式
You're still in Navigation.
谢谢
Thank you.
你帮我做好,再送到abc我办公室好吗?
Look， can you just patch itabcthrough to my office?
-他今天怎么了?-没什么
(coughs)
- What's his problem today?abc- Nothing.
这时间线从12月到2月abc就不连续了
This time line goes straightabcfrom December to February.
-你想做什么,杰克?abc-和你一样,要解决这个问题
- What are you trying to do， Jack?abc- same as you. solve this problem.
我并不是说这个
That's not what l'm talking about.
杰克
Listen， Jack.
我得对你说实话
l'm gonna be honest with you.
你是我的偶像
l look up to you.
必要时我甚至会为你[子弹.abc但现在我必须问清楚
l'd take a bullet for you if l had to，abcbut right now l'm gonna hold the mirror up.
你曾在萨拉扎那里abc做了6个月卧底
You were under with salazar for six months.
我知道他们对你所做的一切
l know what they did to you.
我也知道你对自己做了什么
And l know what you did to yourself.
这些不是一夜之间abc就能摆脱的事情
You can't make that go away overnight.
你认为我不知道吗
You think l didn't know?
你应该管好自己的事情,蔡斯
You should mind your own business， Chase.
我就想说我会支持你
All l'm trying to sayabcis that l'm here for you.
但今天不是让你给abc所有人证明的日子
But today is not the day to tryabcto prove to everybody that you're all better.
马上就要有大麻烦了abc你和我都知道
lt's about to hit the fan.abcYou know that and l know that.
做你该做的事情吧,伙计
so do what you gotta do， man.
清醒一下,继续工作
Get your head straight so we can do our work.
(phone rings)
爸爸,你在上面吗?
Dad, you up there?
爸爸?
Dad?
是的
Yeah.
我能上来吗?我有事跟你说
Can l come up?abcl need to talk to you about something.
Uh...
现在不行,亲爱的.我很忙
Not right now， sweetheart.abcl'm in the middle of something.
好,你有空就叫我吧
OK. Call me when you have a few minutes.
好的
OK.
Visiontext subtitles: Joanna Wilkinson
ENGLlsH sDH